[{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980367148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":20149,"timeElapsed":94678},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980381492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":14341,"timeElapsed":109022},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980393299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":11806,"timeElapsed":120829},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980400259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6959,"timeElapsed":127789},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980416155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":15894,"timeElapsed":143685},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":10631,"timeElapsed":154317},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980430587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3798,"timeElapsed":158117},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":7350,"timeElapsed":165468},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6232,"timeElapsed":171701},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":14621,"timeElapsed":191541},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471067,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":7054,"timeElapsed":198597},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980534651,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":63583,"timeElapsed":262181},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980557019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":22366,"timeElapsed":284549},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":8551,"timeElapsed":293101},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980571892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6319,"timeElapsed":299422},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980574803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2910,"timeElapsed":302333},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980582467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7663,"timeElapsed":309997},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980587556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5088,"timeElapsed":315086},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980598475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8917,"timeElapsed":326005},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980607571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9095,"timeElapsed":335101},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980621235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":13662,"timeElapsed":348765},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637019,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":15783,"timeElapsed":364549},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980644251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":7231,"timeElapsed":371781},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980647731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3478,"timeElapsed":375261},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980651027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3295,"timeElapsed":378557},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4470,"timeElapsed":383029},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980662763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":7263,"timeElapsed":390293},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980665803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3039,"timeElapsed":393333},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980675635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":8820,"timeElapsed":403165},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980684091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":8455,"timeElapsed":411621},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":8670,"timeElapsed":420293},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980704666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":11902,"timeElapsed":432196},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980708227,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3559,"timeElapsed":435757},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980710427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2198,"timeElapsed":437956},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712419,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1991,"timeElapsed":439949},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980726419,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":13999,"timeElapsed":453949},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980736163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":9742,"timeElapsed":463693},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980759627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":8277,"timeElapsed":487157},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980768323,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8695,"timeElapsed":495853},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980776803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":8479,"timeElapsed":504333},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980788867,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":12062,"timeElapsed":516397},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980792971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4103,"timeElapsed":520501},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980801643,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":8671,"timeElapsed":529173},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980805212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3567,"timeElapsed":532742},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980807827,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2614,"timeElapsed":535357},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980823907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":16079,"timeElapsed":551437},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980829027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":5119,"timeElapsed":556557},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6004,"timeElapsed":563781},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980843706,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":7454,"timeElapsed":571236},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980863363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":19655,"timeElapsed":590893},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980872315,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":8951,"timeElapsed":599845},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980876355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4039,"timeElapsed":603885},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980878539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2183,"timeElapsed":606069},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980880227,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1687,"timeElapsed":607757},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980885931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5703,"timeElapsed":613461},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980888219,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":2287,"timeElapsed":615749},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980902019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":9845,"timeElapsed":629549},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980906643,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4622,"timeElapsed":634173},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980918139,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":11495,"timeElapsed":645669},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980920650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2510,"timeElapsed":648180},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980925835,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":5183,"timeElapsed":653365},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980929859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":4023,"timeElapsed":657389},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980932035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2175,"timeElapsed":659565},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980936995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4959,"timeElapsed":664525},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980939675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2678,"timeElapsed":667205},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980950883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7435,"timeElapsed":678413},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980958195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":7311,"timeElapsed":685725},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980964178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5982,"timeElapsed":691708},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980968611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4432,"timeElapsed":696141},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980971898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3286,"timeElapsed":699428},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980974091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2192,"timeElapsed":701621},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980977291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3199,"timeElapsed":704821},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980994867,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":17575,"timeElapsed":722397},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981002707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7839,"timeElapsed":730237},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981022778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":7931,"timeElapsed":750308},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981026178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3399,"timeElapsed":753708},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981032563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6383,"timeElapsed":760093},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981036498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3934,"timeElapsed":764028},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981039299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2799,"timeElapsed":766828},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981041451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2151,"timeElapsed":768981},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981043875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2423,"timeElapsed":771405},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981050946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":7070,"timeElapsed":778476},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981054228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3280,"timeElapsed":781757},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981061691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6709,"timeElapsed":789221},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981064283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2591,"timeElapsed":791813},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981069123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":4839,"timeElapsed":796653},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981075244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":6119,"timeElapsed":802774},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981077475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2230,"timeElapsed":805005},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981079819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2343,"timeElapsed":807349},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981081539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1719,"timeElapsed":809069},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981085803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4263,"timeElapsed":813333},{"subjectID":"jrr10btldz","prolificID":"673a5295a273de4f70ab6ee3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24d895c83fe6e5fc139","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981087403,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1599,"timeElapsed":814933}]